AUGUSTINE OLUWASEUN TITCOMBE

Address: Ibadan, Oyo State, Nigeria (Open to relocation)

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/augustine-titcombe-8577a0107

Tel.: +234 9038276680 Email: titcombeaustine@gmail.com

<u>Career Summary</u>: Analytically driven strong technical personnel, with great professional working etiquette and wonderful hands on job experience(s) in facilities management, general maintenance and sales.

Acquired Skills and Knowledge

- > Maintenance, repair, installation and overhauling of mechanical & electrical equipments: water pumps, gas pumps, inverters, stabilizers, breakers, generators etc
- > Wiring and Plumbing
- > Working knowledge of ISO 9001 & 14001 quality systems
- Computer proficiency e.g SAP ERP and Microsoft Office tools (Excel, Word, & Power Point).

Professional Certifications: Issuing Organization and Date

- > HSE (I, II & III): International Institute of Risk & Safety Management: (IIRSM)/2017
- Certified Project Managers Course: Oil & Gas Education and Research Academy: (OGERA)/2017
- ➤ Basic Fire Safety Course: Oil & Gas Education and Research Academy: (OGERA)/2017
- > Facility Management & Maintenance Technology: (OGERA)/2017

Work Experience

PLANT MANAGER

July 2021 - Present

THE GAS PALACE MEGA LIMITED

- Manage, supervise and coordinate all company's activities, sales and staffs
- Ensures that all units are functional and efficient in the line of their duties
- Gives daily reports of all LPG platform sales and activities to the CEO

PLATFORM SUPERVISOR

Sep 2020 - July 2021

THE GAS PALACE MEGA LIMITED

- Supervised and coordinated all LPG platform activities, sales and staffs
- Ensured that all LPG plant sales are properly distributed and recorded
- Gave daily reports of all LPG platform sales and activities to the General Manager

LPG FACILITIES MAINTENANCE MANAGER

Apr 2019 - Aug 2020

THE GAS PALACE MEGA LIMITED

- Ensured that the basic facilities, such as water pumps, LPG gas pumps, inverters and power generating sets, are well maintained.
- Ensured that the facility meet the government's LPG health and safety regulatory standards.

PRUDENTIAL ZENITH LIFE INSURANCE LIMITED

- Provided advice and sales of Prudential Zenith Life products to customers in Zenith Bank
- Built good relationships with bank branch staff to encourage customer referrals
- Ensured prompt and efficient delivery of policy documents to customers.

PROGRAM ASSISTANT; AGRIBUSINESS

Apr 2016 - Mar 2017

ONELIFE INITIATIVE FOR HUMAN DEVELOPMENT

- Handled all repairs, servicing and installations of all farm equipment/tools
- Managed all Agribusiness related activities, starting from planting to marketing
- Wrote reports and gave recommendations on new farming strategies/techniques.

GENERATOR REPAIR FACILITATOR

Nov 2014 - Nov 2015

SKILL ACQUISITION AND ENTREPRENEURIAL DEVELOPMENT (SAED), NYSC

• Trained corps member on the repair, servicing and overhauling of power generating sets (diesel and petrol engines)

Volunteering Activity

COMMUNITY ADVOCATE

Apr2016 - May 2017

THE GUARDIAN UK

> Advocated against Female Genital Mutilation (FGM); reached out to 352 schools in the designated community within two (2) months.

Academic Qualifications

- > M.Sc., Occupational Health and Safety Management (Merit) South American University, Delaware, USA
- June 2016 Nov 2017

B.Sc., Physics (Second Class Division)
Ekiti State University, Ado Ekiti, Nigeria

Nov 2009 - Aug 2014

Courses

- Basic Time Management
- Fundamental of Data Mining
- Action Planning

- Data Sufficiency
- Advertising & Marketing
- Operations Management

Key Strength and Competence

- Influencing and Negotiating Skill
- Maintenance and equipment repairs
- Dynamic Leadership Skill
- Strong Oral and Writing Skill

- Problem Solving and Analytical Skill
- Customer Service
- Team Player